A Guide to the Richmond Symphony Archives, 1965-1982
Virginia Commonwealth University, James Branch Cabell Library
- Concerts 1973-1981
  - Sinfonia Run-Out: Galax/Lynchburg, Va 1983 (Box-folder 15a.1)
  - Sinfonia Run-Out: Good News Celebration 1983 (Box-folder 15a.2)
  - Sinfonia Run-Out: Quantico, Va 1983 (Box-folder 15a.3)
  - Sinfonia Run-Out: Randolph-Macon with Lillian Kallir (Box-folder 15a.4)
  - Sinfonia Run-Out: Sweet Briar College 1982 (Box-folder 15a.5)
  - Sinfonia Run-Out: Washington and Lee University 1983 (Box-folder 15a.6)
  - Sinfonia Series 1975-1976 (Box-folder 15a.7)
  - Sinfonia Series 1975-1976 (Box-folder 15a.8)
  - Sinfonia Series 1975-1976 (Box-folder 16.1)
  - Sinfonia Series 1975-1976 (Box-folder 16.2)
  - Sinfonia Series 1975-1976 (Box-folder 16.3)
  - Sinfonia Series 1976-1977 (Box-folder 16.4)
  - Sinfonia Series 1976-1977 (Box-folder 16.5)
  - Sinfonia Series 1976-1977 (Box-folder 16.6)
  - Sinfonia Series 1976-1977 (Box-folder 16.7)
  - Sinfonia Series 1976-1977 (Box-folder 16.8)
  - Sinfonia Series 1976-1977 (Box-folder 16.9)
  - Sinfonia Series 1977-1978 (Box-folder 17.1)
  - Sinfonia Series 1977-1978 (Box-folder 17.2)
  - Sinfonia Series 1977-1978 (Box-folder 17.3)
  - Sinfonia Series 1978-1979 (Box-folder 17.4)
  - Sinfonia Series 1978-1979 (Box-folder 17.5)
  - Sinfonia Series 1983-1984 (Box-folder 17.6)
  - Sinfonia Series 1983-1984 (Box-folder 17.7)
  - Sinfonia Series: Candlelight Concert 1975 (Box-folder 17a.1)
  - Sinfonia Series: Evening of Comic Opera 1974 (Box-folder 17a.2)
  - Sinfonia Series: evening of Dance 1974-1975 (Box-folder 17a.3)
  - Sinfonia Series: General Information 1974-1975 (Box-folder 17a.4)
  - Sinfonia Series: Gilgamesh 1982-1983 (Box-folder 17a.5)
  - Sinfonia Series: Karl Haas 1976 (Box-folder 17a.6)
  - Sinfonia Series: Edwin Mirr 1974 (Box-folder 17a.7)
  - Sinfonia Series: Miscellaneous concerts in town 1982-1983 (Box-folder 17a.8)
  - Sinfonia Strings 1983-1984 (Box-folder 17a.9)
  - Soleil Lase Fantasia 1979 (Box-folder 17a.10)
  - Special Program: Peter Schickele 1974 (Box-folder 17a.11)
  - Spring Student Concerts 1980 (Box-folder 17a.12)
  - State Fairgrounds July 4, 1983 (Box-folder 17a.13)
  - String Quartet 1982-1983 (Box-folder 17a.14)
  - Subscription Concert: All Orchestral 1973-1974 (Box-folder 18.1)
  - Subscription Concert: All Orchestral 1980 (Box-folder 18.2)
  - Subscription Concert: Enrique Batiz 1977 (Box-folder 18.3)
  - Subscription Concert: lazar Berman 1975-1977 (Box-folder 18.4)
  - Subscription Concert: Walter Braxton 1975 (Box-folder 18.5)
  - Subscription Concert: T. Briccetti 1980 (Box-folder 18.6)
  - Subscription Concert: James Buswell 1977 (Box-folder 18.7)
  - Subscription Concert: Dale Clevenger 1980 (Box-folder 18.8)
  - Subscription Concert: Jeannette Cross 1977 (Box-folder 18.9)
  - Subscription Concert: Wm. Curry Savely Schuster 1976 (Box-folder 18.10)
  - Subscription Concert: Ingrid Dingfelder 1976-1977 (Box-folder 18.11)
  - Subscription Concert: Rafael Druian 1977-1978 (Box-folder 18.12)
  - Subscription Concert: Philippe Entremont 1975-1976 (Box-folder 18.13)
  - Subscription Concert: An Evening of Opera 1974 (Box-folder 18.14)
  - Subscription Concert: Carole Farley 1976-1978 (Box-folder 18.15)
  - Subscription Concert: Klaus Hellwig 1977-1978 (Box-folder 18.16)
  - Subscription Concert: N. Hinderas, R. Durham 1976 (Box-folder 18.17)
  - Subscription Concert: jerome Hines 1976-1977 (Box-folder 18.18)
  - Subscription Concert: Lorin Hollander 1980 (Box-folder 18.19)
  - Subscription Concert: Young-Uck Kim 1976 (Box-folder 18.20)
  - Subscription Concert: John and Joan Korman 1976-1977 (Box-folder 18.21)
  - Subscription Concert: J. Lewis, R. Durham 1977-1978 (Box-folder 19.1)
  - Subscription Concert: Sergiu Luca 1976-1977 (Box-folder 19.2)
  - Subscription Concert: Sergiu Luca 1977-1978 (Box-folder 19.3)
  - Subscription Concert: Alan Marks 1977 (Box-folder 19.4)
  - Subscription Concert: The Messiah 1977 (Box-folder 19.5)
  - Subscription Concert: Edward A. Mirr 1974 (Box-folder 19.6)
  - Subscription Concert: Jonathan Mott 1975 (Box-folder 19.7)
  - Subscription Concert: Martha and Jonathan Mott 1978 (Box-folder 19.8)
  - Subscription Concert: Jessye Norman 1976-1977 (Box-folder 19.9)
  - Subscription Concert: Norman, McCray, and Shinall 1980 (Box-folder 19.10)
  - Subscription Concert: Garrick Ohlsson 1976-1977 (Box-folder 19.11)
  - Subscription Concert: Pates, Benson, and Britton 1975 (Box-folder 19.12)
  - Subscription Concert: Leonard Pennario 1975-1977 (Box-folder 19.13)
  - Subscription Concert: Ruggiero Ricci 1977-1978 (Box-folder 19.14)
  - Subscription Concert: Richmond Symphony Chorus 1976 (Box-folder 19.15)
  - Subscription Concert: Richmond Symphony Chorus 1978 (Box-folder 19.16)
  - Subscription Concert: Richmond Symphony Chorus 1979 (Box-folder 19.17)
  - Subscription Concert: Pascal Roge 1973-1974 (Box-folder 20.1)
  - Subscription Concert: Aaron Rosand 1973-1975 (Box-folder 20.2)
  - Subscription Concert: Aaron Rosand 1976-1977 (Box-folder 20.3)
  - Subscription Concert: Zina Schiff 1977 (Box-folder 20.4)
  - Subscription Concert: Season Opener 1974 (Box-folder 20.5)
  - Subscription Concert: Barbara Shuttleworth 1974-1975 (Box-folder 20.6)
  - Subscription Concert: Edwin Thayer 1974 (Box-folder 20.7)
  - Subscription Concert: Trio Pro Viva 1979 (Box-folder 20.8)
  - Subscription Concert: G. Tucker, K. Vaught 1977 (Box-folder 20.9)
  - Subscription Concert: Virginia Ballet Theater 1975 (Box-folder 20.10)
  - Subscription Concert: Andre Watts 1974-1975 (Box-folder 20.11)
  - Subscription Concert: Mark Westcott 1980 (Box-folder 20.12)
  - Subscription Concert: Wilson, Mott, and Rosato 1979 (Box-folder 20.13)
  - Subscription Concert: Woodwing Quintet 1978 (Box-folder 20.14)
  - Sunday Matinee Series: General Information 1975 (Box-folder 20.15)
  - Sunday Matinee Series: richard Hayman 1975 (Box-folder 20.16)
  - Sunday Matinee Series: Musical America 1976 (Box-folder 20.17)
  - Sunday Matinee Series: The Romeros 1974-1975 (Box-folder 20.18)
  - Sunday Matinee Series: Donna Turner Smith 1976 (Box-folder 20.19)
  - Sunday Serenades 1976-1977 (Box-folder 20.20)
  - Sunday Serenades: Katherine Hindrelet-Brydon 1976 (Box-folder 20.21)
  - Sunday Serenades: Ann Hobson 1977-1978 (Box-folder 20.22)
  - Sunday Serenades: Ann Migdal 1977 (Box-folder 20.23)
  - Sunday Serenades: Jonathan Mott 1977 (Box-folder 20.24)
  - Sunday Serenades: Guher and Suher Pekinel 1980 (Box-folder 20.25)
  - Sunday Serenades: Quartet 1978 (Box-folder 20.26)
  - Sunday Serenades: Smetana Trio 1980 (Box-folder 20.27)
  - Sunday Serenades: Richard Stoltzman 1977 (Box-folder 20.28)
  - Sunday Serenades: Woodwind Quintet 1979 (Box-folder 20.29)
  - Symphony Anniversary Concert 1976 (Box-folder 21.1)
  - Symphony Serenade 1983-1984 (Box-folder 21.2)
  - Thalhimers: woodwind Quintet 1979 (Box-folder 21.3)
  - Trinity United Methodist Church Concert 1978 (Box-folder 21.4)
  - University of Richmond: Woodwind Concert 1979 (Box-folder 21.5)
  - University of Virginia Concert 1969 (Box-folder 21.6)
  - University of Virginia Concert 1979 (Box-folder 21.7)
  - VBT/Hartford Ballet: Carmina Burana 1979 (Box-folder 21.8)
  - Virginia Center Gala 1981 (Box-folder 21.9)
  - Virginia Home Concert 1975 (Box-folder 21.10)
  - Virginia Museum Concert 1977 (Box-folder 21.11)
  - Virginia Polytechnic Institute 1974-1975 (Box-folder 21.12)
  - Virginia State College Concert: Ann Hobson 1977-1978 (Box-folder 21.13)
  - Vocal Soloists 1973-1974 (Box-folder 21.14)
  - White House Concert: Woodwind Quintet 1977 (Box-folder 21.15)
  - William and Mary Concert 1974 (Box-folder 21.16)
  - William and Mary Concert 1975 (Box-folder 21.17)
  - William and Mary Concert 1976 (Box-folder 21.18)
  - William and Mary Concert 1978 (Box-folder 21.19)
  - William and Mary Series 1982-1983 (Box-folder 21.20)
  - Williamsburg Concert Series 1980-1981 (Box-folder 21.21)
  - Wolf Trap 1979 (Box-folder 21a.1)
  - Wolf Trap 1984 (Box-folder 21a.2)
  - Wolf Trap: Franz Allers 1984 (Box-folder 21a.3)
  - Wolf Trap: Eric Knight and the New Swingle Singers 1984 (Box-folder 21a.4)
  - Wolf Trap: Paul Traver 1984 (Box-folder 21a.5)
  - Woman's Club: Woodwind/Brass Quintet 1978-1979 (Box-folder 21a.6)
  - James Woods High School Concert 1975 (Box-folder 21a.7)
  - Woodwind Quintet 1977-1978 (Box-folder 21a.8)
  - Woodwind Quintet 1982-1983 (Box-folder 21a.9)
  - Woodwind Quintet 1983-1984 (Box-folder 21a.10)
  - WRFK Symphony Broadcasts 1976 (Box-folder 21a.11)
  - Young People's Concerts 1973-1974 (Box-folder 22.1)
  - Youth Concerts 1974-1975 (Box-folder 22.2)
  - Youth Concerts 1975-1976 (Box-folder 22.3)
  - Youth Concerts 1976 (Box-folder 22.4)
  - Youth Concerts (Fall) 1977 (Box-folder 22.5)
  - Youth Concerts 1977 (Box-folder 22.6)
  - Youth Concerts (Spring) 1978 (Box-folder 22.7)
  - Youth Concerts 1978 (Box-folder 22.8)
  - Youth Concerts (Spring) 1979 (Box-folder 22.9)
  - Youth Concerts 1979 (Box-folder 22.10)
  - Youth Concerts: Programs 1976-1979 (Box-folder 22.11)
  - Youth Orchestra Concerts 1973-1974 (Box-folder 22.12)
- Programs/Brochures 1962-1980
  - Brochuces: Announcements and Inserts 1971-1975 (Box-folder 23.1)
  - Brochures: Fund Drives 1964-1977 (Box-folder 23.2)
  - Brochures: Marketing Kit 1974-1975 (Box-folder 23.3)
  - Brochures: Miscellaneous, n.d. 1961, 1974-1976 (Box-folder 23.4)
  - Brochures: Season Schedules 1962-1979 (Box-folder 23.5)
  - Brochures: Symphony Reports 1963-1975 (Box-folder 23.6)
  - Programs 1957-1958 (Box-folder 23.7)
  - Programs 1958-1959 (Box-folder 23.8)
  - Programs 1959-1960 (Box-folder 23.9)
  - Programs 1960-1961 (Box-folder 23.10)
  - Programs 1961-1962 (Box-folder 23.11)
  - Programs 1962-1963 (Box-folder 23.12)
  - Programs 1963-1964 (Box-folder 23.13)
  - Programs 1964-1965 (Box-folder 23.14)
  - Programs 1965-1966 (Box-folder 23.15)
  - Programs 1966-1967 (Box-folder 23.16)
  - Programs 1967-1968 (Box-folder 23.17)
  - Programs 1968-1969 (Box-folder 23a.1)
  - Programs 1969-1970 (Box-folder 23a.2)
  - Programs 1970-1971 (Box-folder 23a.3)
  - Programs 1971-1972 (Box-folder 23a.4)
  - Programs 1972-1973 (Box-folder 23a.5)
  - Programs 1973-1974 (Box-folder 23a.6)
  - Programs 1974-1975 (Box-folder 23a.7)
  - Programs 1975-1976 (Box-folder 23a.8)
  - Programs 1976-1977 (Box-folder 23a.9)
  - Programs 1977-1978 (Box-folder 23a.10)
  - Programs 1978-1979 (Box-folder 23a.11)
  - Programs 1979-1980 (Box-folder 23a.12)
  - Programs: American Pops Festival 1977-1978 (Box-folder 23b.1)
  - Programs: American Pops Festival 1978-1979 (Box-folder 23b.2)
  - Programs: American Pops Festival 1979-1980 (Box-folder 23b.3)
  - Programs: Central National Bank Pops 1975-1978 (Box-folder 23b.4)
  - Programs: lollipop Concerts 1976-1977 (Box-folder 23b.5)
  - Programs: pops Concerts (Box-folder 23b.6)
    1960, 1961, 1970-1973, 1977, 1980
  - Programs: Sinfonia 1972-1980 (Box-folder 23b.7)
  - Programs: Subscription Concerts 1963-1964 (Box-folder 23b.8)
  - Programs: Subscription Concerts 1974-1975 (Box-folder 23b.9)
  - Programs: Subscription Concerts 1975-1976 (Box-folder 23b.10)
  - Programs: Subscription Concerts 1976-1977 (Box-folder 23b.11)
  - Programs: Subscription Concerts 1977-1978 (Box-folder 23b.12)
  - Programs: Subscription Concerts 1978-1979 (Box-folder 23b.13)
  - Programs: Subscription Concerts 1979-1980 (Box-folder 23b.14)
  - Programs: Sunday Matinees 1975-1975 (Box-folder 23b.15)
- Planning/Operations 1965-1982
  - Accoustical Catalogs 1973-1979 (Box-folder 24.1)
  - Advertising 1975-1979 (Box-folder 24.2)
  - American Institute of Musical Studies 1973 (Box-folder 24.3)
  - American Symphony Orchestra League: Fed. Aid 1965-1974 (Box-folder 24.4)
  - American Symphony Orchestra League: Convention 1975 (Box-folder 24.5)
  - American Symphony Orchestra League: Convention 1976 (Box-folder 24.6)
  - Attendance File 1973-1978 (Box-folder 24.7)
  - Auto Insurance Information 1980-1982 (Box-folder 24.8)
  - Ballet: Newspaper Clippings 1979 (Box-folder 24.9)
  - Blues Armory 1975 (Box-folder 24.10)
  - Bookkeeping System and Policy 1979 (Box-folder 24.11)
  - Brass Quintet Services 1982-1983 (Box-folder 24.12)
  - Cable Television 1978-1981 (Box-folder 24.13)
  - Calendar 1981-1983 (Box-folder 24.14)
  - Calendar, correspondence 1983-1984 (Box-folder 24.15)
  - City of Richmond 1970-1976 (Box-folder 24.16)
  - Concert Halls: Brochures, Tickets, and Prices 1979-1981 (Box-folder 24.17)
  - Concerts Pending 1976-1979 (Box-folder 24.18)
  - Concert Series: General Information 1973-1974 (Box-folder 25.1)
  - Contracts 1973-1981 (Box-folder 25.2)
  - Contracts: Parking 1974 (Box-folder 25.3)
  - Contracts of Other Orchestras 1971-1973 (Box-folder 25.4)
  - Claude Dodson 1978 (Box-folder 25.5)
  - Employee W-4 Forms 1972-1979 (Box-folder 25.6)
  - Executive Committee Meetings 1973 (Box-folder 25.7)
  - Executive Committee Meetings 1974 (Box-folder 25.8)
  - Facility and Acoustic Related Letters 1975-1978 (Box-folder 25.9)
  - Fantasy Ball 1976-1977 (Box-folder 25.10)
  - Fantasy Ball 1978 (Box-folder 25.11)
  - Fantasy Ball 1979 (Box-folder 25.12)
  - Fantasy Ball 1980 (Box-folder 25.13)
  - Fashion Show 1977-1978 (Box-folder 25.14)
  - Ford Foundation: Fund Drive and Pledges 1967-1971 (Box-folder 26.1)
  - Ford Foundation: General 1971 (Box-folder 26.2)
  - Ford Foundation: General 1971-1977 (Box-folder 26.3)
  - Ford Foundation Grant 1976-1977 (Box-folder 26.4)
  - Ford Foundation Report 1969-1970 (Box-folder 26.5)
  - Ford Foundation Report 1970-1971 (Box-folder 26.6)
  - Ford Foundation Report 1971-1972 (Box-folder 26.7)
  - Ford Foundation Report 1972-1973 (Box-folder 26.8)
  - Ford Foundation Report 1973-1974 (Box-folder 26.9)
  - Ford Foundation Report 1974-1975 (Box-folder 26.10)
  - Ford Foundation Report 1975-1976 (Box-folder 26.11)
  - Ford Foundation Trust 1979-1980 (Box-folder 26.12)
  - Fundraising 1976 (Box-folder 26.13)
  - General Arts: Newspaper Clippings 1979 (Box-folder 26.14)
  - Guest Artists 1974-1975 (Box-folder 26.15)
  - Guest Artists 1978-1979 (Box-folder 26.16)
  - Guest Artists 1979-1980 (Box-folder 26.17)
  - Guest Conductors 1978-1979 (Box-folder 27.1)
  - Erick Hawkins Dance Company 1976 (Box-folder 27.2)
  - House of Delegates: Appropriations Committee 1975-1978 (Box-folder 27.3)
  - Ibsen Project 1978-1979 (Box-folder 27.4)
  - In-School Concerts: Questionaires 1975 (Box-folder 27.5)
  - Instruments: Brochures, Catalogs 1971-1977 (Box-folder 27.6)
  - Instruments: Harpsichord 1973-1979 (Box-folder 27.7)
  - Instruments: Insurance 1977 (Box-folder 27.8)
  - Instruments: Insurance 1980-1981 (Box-folder 27.9)
  - Insurance: Blue Cross/Blue Shield 1973-1979 (Box-folder 27.10)
  - Insurance: Cancelled Policies 1969-1974 (Box-folder 27.11)
  - Insurance: Certificates 1968-1979 (Box-folder 27.12)
  - Insurance: Correspondence 1974-1978 (Box-folder 27.13)
  - Insurance: General 1974-1977 (Box-folder 27.14)
  - Introductory Packet for New Board Members 1977 (Box-folder 27.15)
  - Junior Board of the Richmond Symphony 1978-1980 (Box-folder 27.16)
  - Librarian: Mildred Mason 1972 (Box-folder 27.17)
  - Library: Symphony-Owned Music 1970-1979 (Box-folder 27.18)
  - Allan Lokos: Sinfonia Artist Management 1978-1979 (Box-folder 27.19)
  - Lyrics: miscellaneous, n.d. (Box-folder 27.20)
  - Magazines, newspaper inserts 1970, 1978 (Box-folder 27.21)
  - Members 1978 (Box-folder 28.1)
  - Member Information Sheets 1971 (Box-folder 28.2)
  - Memorials 1974-1975 (Box-folder 28.3)
  - Memos to Orchestra 1980-1981 (Box-folder 28.4)
  - Mosque: Organ 1980 (Box-folder 28.5)
  - Mosque: Pit Alterations 1979 (Box-folder 28.6)
  - Mosque Rental 1974 (Box-folder 28.7)
  - Music Publishers 1977-1978 (Box-folder 28.8)
  - Music Publishers: Broude Brothers 1977 (Box-folder 28.9)
  - Music Publishers: European American 1981 (Box-folder 28.10)
  - Music Publishers: Miscellaneous 1981 (Box-folder 28.11)
  - Music Purchase 1975 (Box-folder 28.12)
  - Musicians and Board Lists 1975-1977 (Box-folder 28.13)
  - Musicians Club of Richmons 1973-1976 (Box-folder 28.14)
  - NASAA Newsletter 1979 (Box-folder 28.15)
  - Nat'l Endowment for the Arts: Chamber Ensemble 1973 (Box-folder 28.16)
  - Nat'l Endowment for the Arts: Chamber Orchestra 1972 (Box-folder 28.17)
  - Nat'l Endowment for the Arts: Director of Dev. 1973 (Box-folder 28.18)
  - Nat'l Endowment for the Arts: Grant 1974 (Box-folder 28.19)
  - Nat'l Endowment for the Arts: Grant Applications 1974 (Box-folder 29.1)
  - Nat'l Endowment for the Arts: Internship Program 1979 (Box-folder 29.2)
  - Nat'l Endowment for the Arts: Music Program 1975 (Box-folder 29.3)
  - Nat'l Endowment for the Arts: Survey 1973-1976 (Box-folder 29.4)
  - Nominating Committee 1973-1979 (Box-folder 29.5)
  - Notes: Theresa Williamson 1976 (Box-folder 29.6)
  - Office Equipment 1971 (Box-folder 29.7)
  - Office Lease: 112 E. Franklin 1969-1975 (Box-folder 29.8)
  - Office Memos 1975-1976 (Box-folder 29.9)
  - Old Dominion Symphony Concert: Billing Sheets 1974-1977 (Box-folder 29.10)
  - Old Dominion Symphony Council: Questionaire 1974 (Box-folder 29.11)
  - Old Dominion University 1971 (Box-folder 29.12)
  - Opera Alliance of Richmond, n.d. (Box-folder 29.13)
  - Opera and Theater: Newspaper Clippings 1979 (Box-folder 29.14)
  - Orchestra Memos 1982 (Box-folder 29.15)
  - Orchestra Schedules and Memos 1981 (Box-folder 29.16)
  - Personnel Directory: Original 1979-1980 (Box-folder 30.1)
  - Pops Alumni Program 1979-1980 (Box-folder 30.2)
  - Press Releases 1978-1979 (Box-folder 30.3)
  - Press Releases 1980-1981 (Box-folder 30.4)
  - Programs 1974-1975 (Box-folder 30.5)
  - Publicity: Slides 1979 (Box-folder 30.6)
  - Publicity: Symphony Week 1979 (Box-folder 30.7)
  - Quantity Photo Company 1973-1977 (Box-folder 30.8)
  - Radio Station WGOE 1973 (Box-folder 30.9)
  - Recording for Alpha 1975 (Box-folder 30.10)
  - Rehearsal Schedules 1973-1974 (Box-folder 30.11)
  - Rehearsal Schedules 1975-1976 (Box-folder 30.12)
  - Repertoire 1980 (Box-folder 30.13)
  - Report: The Symphony Orchestra Abroad 1970 (Box-folder 30.14)
  - Richmond Ballet 1980 (Box-folder 30.15)
  - Richmond Ballet 1981 (Box-folder 30.16)
  - Richmond Coliseum 1970-1971 (Box-folder 30.17)
  - Richmond Opera Company 1977-1978 (Box-folder 30.18)
  - Richmond Symphony Fact Sheets 1974-1979 (Box-folder 30.19)
  - Run-Outs: Technical Arrangements 1974-1975 (Box-folder 30.20)
  - St. Catherines Creative Arts Program 1977 (Box-folder 31.1)
  - St. Catherines Creative Arts Program 1978 (Box-folder 31.2)
  - St. Catherines Creative Arts Program 1979 (Box-folder 31.3)
  - Schedule: Symphony/Sinfonia 1978-1979 (Box-folder 31.4)
  - Season Ticket Publicity 1976-1977 (Box-folder 31.5)
  - Seasonal Employment 1974-1978 (Box-folder 31.6)
  - Senate: Finance Committee 1975 (Box-folder 31.7)
  - Senate/House of Delegates: Correspondence 1976-1977 (Box-folder 31.8)
  - SERMOM World Premieres 1975-1977 (Box-folder 31.9)
  - Sinfonia: European Tour 1973-1974 (Box-folder 31.10)
  - Sinfonia: Formation, Contract Negotiation 1970-1974 (Box-folder 31.11)
  - Sinfonia: General Information 1974-1975 (Box-folder 31.12)
  - Sinfonia: Memos, Itineraries and Schedules 1977-1978 (Box-folder 31.13)
  - Sinfonia: Technical Arrangements 1978-1979 (Box-folder 31.14)
  - Sinfonia: Tour 1974 (Box-folder 31.15)
  - Sinfonia Series: Correspondence, Articles 1973-1974 (Box-folder 31.16)
  - Social Security 1975 (Box-folder 31.17)
  - Special Audience Project: Federated Arts Council 1978 (Box-folder 31.18)
  - Sponsor: Musicians Club String Orchestra 1979 (Box-folder 31.19)
  - Staff Notes 1980-1981 (Box-folder 31.20)
  - Symphony Personnel: Memos, Member Lists 1972-1978 (Box-folder 32.1)
  - Symphonia Repertoire: Sinfonia 1978-1979 (Box-folder 32.2)
  - Symphony Repertoire and Directory 1979-1980 (Box-folder 32.3)
  - Symphony Schedule 1979-1980 (Box-folder 32.4)
  - Symphony Week 1976 (Box-folder 32.5)
  - Symphony Week 1978 (Box-folder 32.6)
  - Symphony Week 1980 (Box-folder 32.7)
  - Symphony Week 1983-1984 (Box-folder 32.8)
  - Teaching Program 1975 (Box-folder 32.9)
  - Tour: Sinfonia 1977 (Box-folder 32.10)
  - Union Contracts and Negotiations 1970-1977 (Box-folder 32.11)
  - University of Richmond 1972 (Box-folder 32.12)
  - Virginia Ballet Theatre 1976-1979 (Box-folder 32.13)
  - Va. Commission for the Arts and Humanities 1973-1975 (Box-folder 32.14)
  - Va. Commission for the Arts and Humanities 1975 (Box-folder 32.15)
  - Va. Commission for the Arts and Humanities 1975-1976 (Box-folder 32.16)
  - Va. Commonwealth Grant 1977 (Box-folder 32.17)
  - Va. Commonwealth In-School Program Expansion 1976 (Box-folder 32.18)
  - Virginia Commonwealth University 1970-1974 (Box-folder 32.19)
  - Virginia State Department of Education 1974 (Box-folder 32.20)
  - Wind Quintet Services 1982-1983 (Box-folder 32.21)
  - Women's Committee 1972-1976 (Box-folder 33.1)
  - Women's Committee 1976-1977 (Box-folder 33.2)
  - Women's Committee Auction 1969-1971 (Box-folder 33.3)
  - Women's Committee Auction 1974-1975 (Box-folder 33.4)
  - Women's Committee By-Laws 1975-1977 (Box-folder 33.5)
  - Women's Committee Guest Speaker: Audrey Baird 1975-1977 (Box-folder 33.6)
  - Workman's Compensation Information 1976-1983 (Box-folder 33.7)
  - Youth Orchestra 1971-1981 (Box-folder 33.8)
  - Youth Orchestra: Summer Camp 1975-1977 (Box-folder 33.9)
- Correspondence 1973-1982
  - Correspondence 1973 (Box-folder 34.1)
  - Correspondence 1973-1974 (Box-folder 34.2)
  - Correspondence, January-March 1976 (Box-folder 34.3)
  - Correspondence, April-June 1976 (Box-folder 35.1)
  - Correspondence, July-September 1976 (Box-folder 35.2)
  - Correspondence, October-December 1976 (Box-folder 35.3)
  - Correspondence, January-March 1977 (Box-folder 35.4)
  - Correspondence, April-June 1977 (Box-folder 35.5)
  - Correspondence, July-September 1977 (Box-folder 36.1)
  - Correspondence, October-December 1977 (Box-folder 36.2)
  - Correspondence 1978 (Box-folder 36.3)
  - Correspondence 1979 (Box-folder 36.4)
  - Correspondence 1980 (Box-folder 36.5)
  - Correspondence 1980 (Box-folder 37.1)
  - Correspondence 1980 (Box-folder 37.2)
  - Correspondence 1981 (Box-folder 37.3)
  - Correspondence 1982 (Box-folder 37.4)
  - Correspondence 1982 (Box-folder 38.1)
  - Correspondence: General Audience 1975-1977 (Box-folder 38.2)
  - Correspondence: Media and Public Relations 1979-1980 (Box-folder 38.3)
- Oversized Materials
- Scrapbook 1960s, oversized (Box 1)
- Scrapbook 1957, oversized (Box 2)
- Loose Clippings, oversized (Box 2)
- LP records
- Orchestre Symphoniqe De Liege, Jacques Houtmann, conductor (signed by Houtmann), oversized
- Richmond Symphony, Jacques Houtmann, conductor, oversized
- Richmond Symphony, Jacques Houtmann, conductor (signed by Houtmann), oversized